In this clip we are going to discuss how to travel with your fish for a short distance and time.
I recommend this being an hour or less.
This is also a similar way that you will be buying a fish from a pet store how they travel.
I recommend you taking your fish out of the tank prior to bagging him up so that he doesn't get all stressed out whenever you take him and put him in the bag.
You can buy these bags at convenient stores.
You are going to open up your plastic bag.
If you buy it yourself, I recommend you take or have a bucket or bowl, put your bag inside once you get it filled up and get your fish in.
You open up your bag, fill it up with the water, make sure you have enough room for air.
As you can see, I did.
Make sure there are no holes in the bag.
I recommend not feeding your fish 24 hours prior to transport him for traveling.
Then you just dump your fish in there.
What you do is make sure you have air for your fish, get a rubber band and you just want to put your rubber band on the top so the water stays in.